{
    "subject": "resource/Tamara_(2005_film)",
    "predicate": "http://xmlns.com/foaf/0.1/name",
    "object": "Tamara",
    "human_readable": "The name of Tamara (2005 film) is Tamara.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9860154390335083,
            "question": "Is there a film titled 'Tamara' from 2005?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8101922869682312,
            "question": "Who directed the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7936643362045288,
            "question": "What is the name of the 2005 film?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7598398923873901,
            "question": "What is the plot of the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7340388894081116,
            "question": "When was the film Tamara released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7330043911933899,
            "question": "What genre is the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5956625938415527,
            "question": "Where was the film Tamara filmed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5775660276412964,
            "question": "Who are some of the actors in the film Tamara?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5228945016860962,
            "question": "Does the film Tamara have any sequels?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.27009445428848267,
            "question": "What is the name of the main character in the film?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The name of Tamara (2005 film) is Tamara.",
            "html": "dbpedia_3810_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Does the film Tamara have any sequels?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3810_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some of the actors in the film Tamara?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3810_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Where was the film Tamara filmed?",
            "html": "dbpedia_3810_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_150.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_156.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_21.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_39.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_44.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_67.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_69.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_88.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_3810_9.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the evaluation of the triple \"The name of Tamara (2005 film) is Tamara\" based on the provided context information:\n\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n\nThis answer is justified because all the documents mention that the title of the 2005 horror film directed by Jeremy Haft and starring Jenna Dewan, Katie Stuart, Chad Faust, Claudette Mink, Melissa Elias, and Matthew Marsden is indeed \"Tamara\"."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information about the 2005 horror film titled \"Tamara,\" which confirms that the name of the film in question is indeed \"Tamara.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "Less Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}